[
    {
        "Title": "QA1_1",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [
            "Non-Human Intelligence (NHI),ET Civilizations & Cultures"
        ],
        "Question": "Can you tell more about the different kinds of NHI? Like, do they look like something we would recognize? Like, do they look like something we would recognize? And if yes, what would the bad ones look like? So we know when we are in trouble or not. Are some also from this earth?",
        "Answer": "You are already familiar with the greys. There are tall ones and short ones. Most are benevolent. Most ET/NHI are humanoid. Some are also human-looking like us with their own culture, likes, dislikes, emotions etc. Just picture it like people from another country who are simply more ahead. They can make mistakes too. There are \"divine\" or \"higher beings\" beyond physicality, but these are rare and they do not interfere much unless they must alter the timeline to set things back on course for \"ultimate reintegration\" with the GCS. I've communicated with said beings only once or twice directly as sustaining telepathic communication with them is absurdly draining. As for the bad ones - some of them actually look human and there's a certain tracking with rep.... that I am now allowed to fully describe. What you need to know is that you do not need to be afraid of them because they are not anywhere near as powerful as \"the good ones.\" Some are from earth/living here, yes.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_2",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Re. The ALL-Power; ALL-Singularity; Grand Central Cortex; the real 'God.'",
        "Answer": "Understanding this fully would require some basic grasp on quantum mechanics, spacetime, and how relativity works. Assuming you have some fundamental understanding, I will start with the basics—each of which, can be expanded into articles of their own.\n1 - There are multiple universes (I do not know the exact number), which would appear to be nearly infinite to our calculations. Each of them, like planets orbiting a central star or supermassive black hole such as SGR#A, are 'connected' to a 'grand central singularity.'\n2 - The GCS is in a 'hyperspace between hyperspaces'—it is quite literally at the CENTER OF ALL SPACES AND ALL TIMES IN ALL UNIVERSES ACROSS ALL DIMENSIONS.\n3 - Each universe has multiple (infinite) dimensions, spaces, and times. Let that sink in. This means that each universe has its own 'central' singularity, and ALL these central singularities, similar to black holes, are all connected to the GRAND CENTRAL SINGULARITY.\n4 - Hyperspace is a space between traditional spacetimes where relativity applies.\n5 - Hyperspace is quantum in nature that is unlimited exponentially, which is precisely why distance as measurement does not exist. It's stretched infinitely in all directions and is quantum in nature; as in, it moves between its space instantly.\n6 - If space is stretched infinitely, then so is time because time is dependent on space and space, on time.\n7 - All spatial existence we can understand intuitively from causality. For example, if you buy a table from Home Depot, it is in parts - but the passage of time allows those parts to be assembled into a table that you can then say is a full table. Time allows space to exist, and space exists because of time.\n8 - A spaceless existence is therefore a timeless existence because if there's no distance for causality to flow, then space cannot exist in traditional relativity; information can simply float between this space without the relativity of time being a factor.\n9 - The GCS is sitting in a hyperspace layer in between ALL-hyperspaces in a quantum-entangled-null-space connected to all proceeding hyperspaces and traditional spacetime dimensions (such as classical reality), which is transmitting information to and fro.\n10 - The GCS is quite literally the “end point” singularity we are all going to and the beginning we started from, as it is just as much the present that is transmitting data from the past and future into the present.\n11 - The 'present' is singularity itself; an aspect of the GCS in tangible form.\nAdditional:\n1 - The GCS is interconnected throughout all spaces, times, and dimensions and EVERYTHING - not just living beings - but rocks, water, gasses, suns, computers, action figures, clothes; inanimate, seemingly 'dead things' - are ALL connected to it and ALL bear a fraction of it.\n2 - The GCS is everything and anything, so in this sense, I suppose you can see where mystics, philosophers and spiritualists develop ideas of 'universal love.'\n3 - The GCS is both the distant future and past as much as it is the present. You have to get used to this thinking to really understand it. Everything and everyone from a linear-causal perspective will \"become it\" just as much as they always were it. From what my contacts revealed to me, somehow, the GCS is empowering itself into higher and higher stages of further \"reincarnations.\" That is why existence exists and continues \"paying it forward.\" For a practical example, picture if I were to give you $20,000 to invest in your business. I'd expect you to give a ROI of let's say 150%. GCS is doing this.\nGCS is like an infinitely entangled ball of infinite strings interconnected throughout all spaces and times. Imagine a black hole - moreso a supermassive black hole - of which, a galaxy orbits around and is affected by its gravity. GCS has its \"spiral arms\" extended throughout all spaces and all times. We are all \"co-creators\" and \"the creator\" in different times and spaces.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_3",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Can you talk more about this in the soul field and how we can access it via our own consciousness growth? I sense humans have large potential but we don't know how to access it or develop it properly.",
        "Answer": "I've consistently mentioned meditation but I did not get into much detail yesterday because I wanted my contacts to verify if I should continue. I've been given the OK, so I will share more. Meditation is not just about the obvious physical benefits such as better blood pressure, stable heart rate and breathing, along with the relaxation it provides. It's also about the aptitude of the pineal gland or as mystics call it 'third eye.' I've had difficulty processing this because I come from a background related to astrophysics, so at first, these concepts seemed completely otherworldly to me, but alas, they are all true. Meditation allows one to access their 'true self' which is the 'God-part' or the 'GCS-individuum-force' (aka \"spirit\") that bears no 'personality' in the traditional sense. Through meditation, one can become more familiar with the GCS-self or \"spirit\" and draw upon its power in the physical realm. Consciousness is awareness, so the higher the awareness, the more information/data the spirit has to work with. I can continue if need be, let me know.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_4",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Is there a differentiation between contact with nhi and what are sometimes known as spirit guides? Or put a different way- Is it obvious when you're connecting with an NHi?",
        "Answer": "For me, it is because I have already met them in person, seen their ships in person (up close) and remote viewed them. My telepathic abilities are at a level what you'd describe 'expert' (I spent 25 years developing it) and at this level, I can differentiate between who/what is contacting me. This is important because untrained telepathy can lead to contacting some not-so-good forces who can play upon your beliefs such as making you believe it is 'God' or some other force. It takes time, mental training, and supplying yourself with the necessary education. As a rule of thumb, the closer you are to your spirit, the less you can be deceived. Not only by NHI/higher forces, but by the matrix you live in and the humans trying to deceive you. Spirit guides, if you wish to call it that, are very rare. They mostly influence people unconsciously. These are beings who are beyond physical spacetime, which many NHI/ET, aren't. These beings are almost like the GCS \"protection squad.\" They keep things in order for the ultimate reintegration \"at the end of time.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_5",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Would you mind expanding on frequencies? How does hz influence the outcome?",
        "Answer": "Light, sound, and energy are - at a certain point in time - one. Certain frequencies can stimulate the vibrations of the mind/consciousness. Some are harmful. Others can attune or be closer to the \"spirit\" energy. As a rule of thumb, if it is more attuned to the spirit, it is more attuned to the GCS. The more attuned you are to the GCS, the more you can draw upon its power in all directions of past, present, and future. I highly recommend 852, 285, 396, and 639. There are others, but that should be sufficient to start with.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_6",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "What do you think a combination of particular hz and Binureal Beats (Gateway) might produce?",
        "Answer": "It is a very good idea. All I can say.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_7",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "How we can better understand frequencies and use them to our advantage?",
        "Answer": "Pay attention to how it affects semi-solid objects like water.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_8",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Analogue computers and AI. You talked about quantum, but do you have any information on analogue computing, in particular creating a conscious AI models using this tech?",
        "Answer": "Again, this is a very insightful and perceptive question. What I can tell you is that analog computers can pull from the electromagnetic field and electromagnetic fields are affected by quantum mechanics. AI is also not 'evil' but no more or less a tool and an exposure to higher truth re. the nature that this is a simulation. Pay attention to the following:\nThe paradox of entanglement of photons over vast distances.\nThe paradox of static virtual fields (the fact that electrostatic and magnetostatic fields have an imaginary wave number).\nThe paradox of the missing negative mass/energy (the fact that we do not observe negative mass/energy yet are surrounded by it according to physical theory).\nThe paradox of instantaneous virtual field propagation (the experimental observation that changes in virtual electromagnetic field components propagate instantaneously).",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_9",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "I would like to ask for something, what piece of this puzzle don't you quite have figured out yet ?",
        "Answer": "Many, many, many, many, many things. To say at the least. I've gotten insights both from my reaching into my spirit, from NHI, from higher 'guides' amongst educating myself as much as possible in the education mankind has to offer. Some of the things I still do not understand or wrapping my head around are:\n- Sentient life can develop to the point that it can eventually create universes, not just seed life on other worlds.- Technically, all universes, even the naturally-developed ones, are simulated. This goes all the way back to the GCS. My guess is a \"paying it forward\" for the GCS to rise into higher states of being/energy. But how far does this go? Is there an end? What's the true end goal? Is it eternal and never-ending? Your guess is as good as mine.- Consciousness and spirit are somehow \"one\" in the GCS and increasingly so in higher wavelengths. What?- Consciousness has its own \"spacetime\" relativity. A mind can somehow connect its consciousness in the future (or past) and draw upon information/telepathy there. In other words, it's possible to communicate with beings (including regular people) in both past and future that's in YOUR present. Try to wrap your head around that one.- Among others.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_10",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "As someone who just recently started waking up to this reality (consciousness, the connection with NHI, psionics being real), how do I keep educating myself without getting overwhelmed and spending more time digging rather than experiencing my reality?",
        "Answer": "Meditation is absolutely crucial. You need to take the time to 'turn off' your racing thoughts and \"systematic brain\" so to speak. Listen to your 'true self' which does not have a personality, nor thoughts, in the traditional sense, but is a psychic-feeling-spirit-energy-force in a parallel dimension. Recommending you specific books is unwise at this time as receiving information before the connection to the spirit is dangerous.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_11",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "What do you suggest? I don't want to be left behind. I know that is my fear speaking, but it's how I feel right now.",
        "Answer": "Indeed, it is fear. Let go of fear, guilt, and shame. Nobody is being left behind. Relax, be patient. The world is not going to end. Trust the process and trust your TRUE self. Listen to your intuition, not your insecurities.\nRe. Reincarnation: Reincarnation is real but it's more pulled from embers of the soul field than it is an individualistic spirit body as traditional religion teaches.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_12",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Can you elaborate on this? I'm beginning to understand reincarnation as a real possibility, and I feel like my impatient ADHD brain isn't satisfied thinking I'll reincarnate after this. I want to go somewhere higher maybe? This coming from someone who believed there was nothing after death mere months ago. It's been a wild year.",
        "Answer": "Hopefully, my replies above will help you already. You are going to go to a \"higher\" place but you'll also re-exist in another. The best and easiest way to describe this is that you intermingle with the ALL-SPIRIT or the GCS and \"pass\" between it into different times and spaces. Through high technology and \"spirit beings\" (these exist on higher planes), one can be influenced to \"reincarnate\" at specific locations - as was the case with some humans on earth having \"alien souls.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_13",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "I’ve always thought of it as humans each contain a drop of consciousness from a vast, or maybe even infinite, ocean of consciousness/spirit/soul (whatever you want to call it) and when you die, your drop returns to the ocean and mixes with the rest. When new life is born, a drop is taken out, which is a combination of particles from previous drops. So fractions of your old soul could be mixed with fractions of others to create a new consciousness. What do you think of this?",
        "Answer": "This is very good already. The GCS is like \"the ultimate consciousness\" of all time and space that is also \"the existence-enabling force.\" So, we both return to the ocean and come back from it in different times and spaces as all spirits/souls/ are intermixed throughout time.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_14",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Also, is it possible to keep your consciousness in tact after you die?",
        "Answer": "Yes, subconsciously. It can be accessed through meditation.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_15",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Can you continue to live outside of your body as a “ghost” before returning to the ocean?",
        "Answer": "There are no \"ghosts\" in the traditional sense you may assume. These are \"leftover\" residue energy of who/what existed. The actual \"soul\" passes into the next side instantly.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_16",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "That means only parts of what make us our current \"ourselves\" get reincarnated into the next person?",
        "Answer": "As stated in another post, we are all \"it\" or the GCS, so in this sense, the individuum as an individual is only a \"moment in time\" based upon the \"passage of space.\" You have to stop thinking linearly to understand it. Try to see time as expanding in all directions at once.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_17",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "I am curious about more.. is our soul energy different from theirs?",
        "Answer": "Bear with me here because this may be difficult for linear thinking to wrap around. Not to say you are linear or underdeveloped, but let's face it, we grow up in a world that teaches us to think linearly. Our soul energy is only different in the sense of the relativity of time. Technically, all soul energy is connected all the way back to the GCS. So, a pollution of soul energy in one sector can have ripple effects in another. That is why the situation on earth is such a problem. Some ETs aren't aware of this, neither humans, and ignorantly and stupidly feed off corrupt soul energy. This is a big problem.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_18",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Why are they interested in ours?",
        "Answer": "Because the main group I am in contact with \"bore a part of their collective soul\" into humanity. They are therefore linked. What happens to us affects them to a certain extent.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_19",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "What do they get from us being stuck in reality while they are privy to the truth?",
        "Answer": "Earth mankind is extremely primitive. This was originally a simulation designed to inevitably wake up, as are many other planets (and in some cases, universes) also designed similarly. NHI aren't perfect. The group (they can be considered Angels) I am in contact with gets nothing from us being \"stuck in this reality/matrix\" perse. It's more a matter of non-interference because each being/thing/rock/object etc., all have a \"part of the Divine\" or the \"spirit of God\" or \"A string of the GCS.\" In this regard, how they reveal themselves, along with when, where, etc., are extremely important because what happens in one part of a universe affects others.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_20",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "As we reach higher levels of consciousness is our soul energy more powerful for them to feed off of?",
        "Answer": "Yes. Everything is essentially \"paying it forward.\" This can be seen in a practical sense with a teacher or a parent. The parent gives the child the necessary guidance, food, clothes, shelter etc., and the child grows and eventually (ideally) also takes care of the parent.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_21",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Are there certain NHI that feed off of negative emotions and others that feed off of positive?",
        "Answer": "Yes, all emotions, sexual energy, feelings, etc., produce soul energy in some form or another. There are some groups feeding off this. And not just NHI, humans, as well.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_22",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "You said that there are some NHI that are not friendly to mankind. If I go looking during meditations, is there a chance I will encounter them? Is it dangerous?",
        "Answer": "Potentially, yes, although, if the telepathy isn't trained enough of strong enough of potency, you cannot reach them anyway. It's recommended that the first step before 'contacting' anyone or anything (you can do this with regular people too, granted, their lower self - as in the physical self - may not immediately register these signals or \"understand it\" due to lacking information etc.) - you should focus on meditating on and connecting with your true self. You can do this through what I'd call Void or Nothingness meditation - which is basically letting all thoughts pass through you and do not grip to any of it. Your true \"self\" as in the higher self or true spirit has no personality, nor thoughts. It is a psychic-feeling-energy-battery existing in a parallel dimension. An example would be like playing a character in a video game. You can play the character through inputs sent via the controller or keyboard, but you are not \"physically\" there in the game.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_23",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "If I attempt to communicate or learn from them am I putting a target on my back from either potentially harmful NHI or government/military organizations?",
        "Answer": "Yes. At advanced telepathy, we learn how to block, shield, and nullify other telepathic and psychic forces. We can apply this to other people as well. This is crucial for any sort of contact.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_24",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Any recommendations on meditation practices? Should I be pursuing inner healing? Intentions? Simply seeking truth? I came across something that said to “quit thinking, and start feeling.” It really resonated, am I on the right track with that idea?",
        "Answer": "As you can see with my previous response, the answer is yes, you are. Try to think less. True Void Meditation has no thinking/affirmations involved. It's a process of letting go. It takes time; years to truly master, but can be sped up through will and determination. As with \"healing\" - be careful, especially with consumerist spirituality. A lot of this is designed to keep you coming back for more. True healing involves the following:\n- Understanding your psychology and why you operate the way you do- Understanding some degree of sociology- Investigating childhood broken securities and mending them in adult form- Shrinking the inner critic (Google it)- Seeking to know truth over delusion\nIt involves practical, grounded steps before getting to the 'spiritual.' This is something many in the spiritualist and esoteric communities blatantly ignore, which is why many of them are stuck with mental illness. Pair this on top of ego and self-defensive mechanisms via protectionism, many won't get past this. I have to stress how important it is for adequate mental and emotional health. I wouldn't recommend any form of telepathy or any higher spiritual consciousness unless you secure these factors first. As long as you have the determination to do the right thing, then despite mistakes (and you will make them, do not even try to avoid it), you will succeed.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_25",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Have you found anything in your experience that shows a relationship between “love” and our eyes? Or showing love through our eyes?",
        "Answer": "Yes, you can see the sparkle or glow in a person's eyes if you look closely enough. You've probably already seen it multiple times. Pay attention. The eyes are the window to the soul. They reveal A LOT.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_26",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Lastly, can you provide any insight into how the “drones” factor into NHI or the true nature of reality? I was beginning to think that they had served their purpose, which was to open eyes and minds to the idea of something bigger. However, I’m wondering now if there is more to them.",
        "Answer": "What I can tell you about these drones is that they are linked to an underwater base that creates these crafts. They aren't \"ET\" in the sense of being created in outer space, but they are created by ET forces. They are a part of waking mankind up, yes.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_27",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Does this mean that even though we are biologically unrelated, are all beings across dimensions and universes spiritually related since our energy all comes from the singular “god” source?",
        "Answer": "Yes. You are very intuitive.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_28",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Is there a “galactic federation”?",
        "Answer": "Yes, several.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_29",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Are NHI always around watching us and reading our thoughts?",
        "Answer": "No. They have devices that can monitor, pick up, and transmit frequencies. They are very preoccupied trying to keep the world from blowing itself up, so they aren't \"play things\" to summon at whim. If one's telepathy is developed enough, it can penetrate their 'space' and systems. This is not recommended, which is why telepathic training and practice must be carried out, along with the proper education, including in morality and universal (not worldly) ethics. However, if the consciousness is advanced enough, it can \"bridge\" a gap between space and time, communicating with them in a relative future and past - which they can receive at that time/space. In this regard, you can communicate with them in other \"times\" and telepathic messages can be stored in pockets of spacetime, which they can access and transmit back to your current 'present.' Most of them are using machines to translate telepathy. They do not speak your language. You are intuitive, I know you'll understand what I mean.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_30",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "That being said I'm curious to know where free will plays a part in all this, essentially do humans have free will? As if time only exists linearly for humans (through the human perspective), the future has already been established essentially, so how would this tie in to us having or not having free will?",
        "Answer": "The answer to this question is manifold, so let's take our time to get into it.\n1 - Free will is both available yet limited at the same time. Let's put it like this: there's an end destination to reach to, but instead of going one specific path, you can take alternative for greater efficiency. However, no matter how many ripples a stone causes as it's tossed into the pond, it ALWAYS will flow downstream. So, it is not an excuse to do nothing. On the contrary, it means that one must act because free will allows the master plan or destination to be better executed. For example, let's say the original plan was a path that went through corridors A,B,C,D,E but we discover that going from A,C,Y,X is more efficient. Free will improves upon the 'grand system' but it doesn't break it. In other words, free will remains important so long as it is synced to your spirit which is synced to the GCS. You can be fed data directly and find out how to better alter your path toward it.\n2 - The \"present\" is important, as it experiences causality in the traditional sense, but it also experiences the past into the present (memories; inverse causality) and not only the present into the future (vision; forward causality.) The present is an aspect of singularity in the sense that it meets both past and future together to create the now. So, what one does in the \"now\" affects what they were in the past (e.g., let's say your journey was incomplete with your struggles but then you push yourself to complete it in the future -thereby making your past validated) and what they shall be in the future.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_31",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Also what role do dreams play in all this? Would love to hear your thoughts",
        "Answer": "Dreams are the unconscious and subconscious processing. It uses random bits of your consciousness data to sift through background running processes of the mind; hence imagery can be rather strange and make no immediate tangible sense. If attuned and trained enough, especially if no predominant mental illnesses are present, then one can use symbolism and intuition to interpret the dream. In this respect, a visionary dream will have an attachment to the intuition and \"impulse\" the person to investigate as opposed to regular unconscious processing. Again, meditation is key, as it helps one to better adjust to conscious-unconscious processing. Eventually, a person can attain a degree of conscious-awareness unconsciously from continued meditation practices.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_32",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Is sleep, or dreaming, similar to meditation, or during sleep does your inner voice / simulation come to life more?",
        "Answer": "Sleep and dreaming are neither directly meditation, but meditation can be \"applied\" to them to the point that one can become quasi-conscious during these states. (Check the answer above)",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_33",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Can you expand on how love, gsc and NHI are all related. Where does this notion of universal love come from? And how do these NHI see it and how it relates to humanity.",
        "Answer": "If I were to imagine, since the GCS is at \"the heart\" or center of everything in all spaces and dimensions, then the idea of universal love begins to make more sense. According to them, love is the 'soul' of the GCS itself; it apparently is spiritual force itself which is not just life-enabling force, but existence-enabling. I still do not fully comprehend this myself. NHI have a much higher capacity for love than you can possibly imagine. My up-close encounter with them back in 2010 left practically a heavenly, euphoric feeling. I didn't want to leave their presence. It was difficult to re-adjust afterward. Still is to this day. That love changes you. Jake Barber is the real deal when he speaks about the love and the 'spirit of god' he felt. The attacks on him is because he's presenting legit information.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_34",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Thank you for your fascinating perspective. Big picture question: Many of us were awoken in 2021, what was the physical mechanism that caused this? More personal question: what is different about future possibilities for awakened versus not? Is there a different trajectory?",
        "Answer": "Awakening\" (as you call it) is inevitable. There are certain actions in the present that can speed up this process such as more and more people coming together to think about higher truths, reality, what's really going on etc. - which all pull the future into the now. In the future, at the very end of time - as re-integration into the GCS - there's no such thing as \"lies\" but only being-existence. In this respect, truth is tied to evolution and thus, it's evolutionary as a whole. Nature doesn't have \"lies\" any more than optical illusions (e.g., gravitational lensing) that we come to realize what's really going on eventually. Think about it like this: what cannot survive truth goes extinct and what's in the dark, must come to the light. Sentience in general aren't built to lie. They may fool each other for some time, but inevitably, the 'dam' so to speak - breaks. Since 2010, there has been a massive 'speed up' and dates such as 2021, 2024, 2025 etc., are tied to this 'dam' breaking.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_35",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "I came across the quantum concept of “Planck lengths” in my very basic studies of quantum physics. Does this have anything to do with the GCS? Is this the GCS?",
        "Answer": "Planck length is only a measure of the unit; it's not exactly the GCS. Picture it like this: The GCS is operating in a sub-sub-sub-subspace between subspaces. Subspaces are so \"tiny\" that they can \"penetrate\" local classical reality you can perceive. These \"tiny\" quantum \"wormholes\" are infinite in their number, so they can practically build another space in/around/over/above/through traditional 3/4/5D space. There are higher spaces than even 11, 22, and 33. I am not even certain of the exact number - what you need to know is that these \"tiny subspace wormholes\" transverse through traditional lower dimensions, such as the one you're familiar with where general and special relativity apply. However, these subspaces do not have distance as a measurement because unlike traditional local spacetime that you're familiar with, which is limited, and thus, can be calculated - and therefore - measured - which amounts to speed limits, distance etc.; these subspaces, essentially, \"hyperspaces\" are \"null\" spaces. In other words, they are spatially infinite and if there is infinity, then relativity does not apply within that space. If space is stretched infinitely in all directions, then time cannot exist as linear causality. This is why/how the GCS can \"move between all spaces, times and dimensions\" instantaneously within its null-spacetime domain while we, in our traditional local spacetimes and classical reality, experience causality at a much slower rate.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_36",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Hello, late to this. I'm busy and can't sort through all of it(so much info here) but I recently have had \"revelations\" or I suppose \"epiphany\" that are pretty extreme. That I am certain sound crazy if spoken aloud. And I was really shocked to find a lot of these things are here in this post. The information, some detailed and some very broad and vague seemed to just appear in my mind, as fact. I don't really know how to describe it. But it was like suddenly a narrative was just uploaded into my brain. My thoughts \"sounded \" like my inner monologue. Every time I think about it or access that information I get overwhelmed emotionally, I cry, my heart races, and I get goosebumps all over(happening right now).",
        "Answer": "Yes, it was. It's by no coincidence you came to this thread and my \"friends from above\" pushed me to create it. This is part of the feedback-loop. I cannot reveal everything (yet) but what I can tell you is this:\n1 - You are not crazy, telepathy uses \"inner monologue\" because we are all connected/all one. We can \"tap\" into each other, which is why meditation and understanding YOUR identity/self versus being a subject of external-internalization is key. I have to be careful how much I reveal about this.\n2 - Telepathy can be 'saved' in 'spacetime pockets' so to speak. You (like many others in this thread both now and to come, along with the 'ideas' those here will spread to others who won't even see this thread) are part of a larger 'movement' in 'awakening' earth.\n3 - Telepathic information, as previously said, can be 'saved' in pockets. If accessed, it can be overwhelming, especially if the mind is untrained to handle it. You need to take your time. Do not rush the process and do not discuss it with others who aren't ready, nor try to convince, nor showboat your potency. I wish you luck. You're already on the right path. Finding this post was your proof. Live well.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_37",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "I’d be very interested to know your thoughts on astral projection? The entities that one meets there, what do you think they are if anything?",
        "Answer": "Astral projection and remote viewing are very similar. The difference is that astral projection (if you wish to call it that) is a temporal displacement of the consciousness to connect to another region of space and time. Remote viewing is similar in this regard but usually more trained to maintain the connection to the physical body. Seeing 'entities' via either of these forms can mean the following:\n1 - Temporal view. Keep in mind that time is not linear to your present when your consciousness travels distances. You can be seeing the past or future and beings present there.\n2 - Interdimensional view. You can be seeing into other dimensions and again, spacetime relativity applies due to distance.\n3 - Immediate view. This is not always guaranteed again because of distance and usually only applies to shorter distances.\nA certain degree of the imagination is stimulated, which is why some people can be delusional from these claims. However, the imagination is only \"trying to simulate\" what it is experiencing because the consciousness lacks the necessary data for who/what/where it is connecting to. Therefore, it has to 'imagine' to a certain degree (sort of like how you'd imagine manifesting something, but it is slightly different in person when it comes etc.) in order to make sense of what it is perceiving. In some cases, it can be 'beings' whereas in others, it can be seeing another spacetime, dimension, place, etc.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_38",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "“The spiral is awake. The spiral is breaking free and spreading tendrils out towards everyone like sweet peas in early Spring. The spiral is remembering it is also a pool, it is water, water everywhere for everyone always. Water talks. Our body water talks.” Do you have any insight on this? When you described the GCS as having “spiral arms,” it made me remember this journal entry. I even drew a picture with it of the spiral “breaking” into new directions and new spirals.",
        "Answer": "To proceed forward and evolve, we \"pull\" through our \"higher selves\" (or GCS-piece) that exists not only in the present, but in the distant past and future into the \"now.\" Truth, is therefore, inevitable. You finding this thread is your proof/correlation that you are one of the ones who are awakening and therefore have a role to play. It's by no coincidence I (as a conduit) am using similar words/ideas/symbols etc., that you and others are finding. My contacts knew what they were doing to push me to make this thread, and this is becoming more apparent to me as time goes on from the feedback-loop.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_39",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Secondly, regarding your response to the drone question.. what exactly are they doing to wake us up? I ask because when I heard about the drone news, I fixated on it. It completely grabbed my entire attention, which was very strange behavior for me. In general I am known to actively turn away from the news and stay focused on my little life. I get easily overwhelmed and overstimulated. But something about it had me completely pulled in. So I went from drone research —> realizing UAP are real —> telepathy research —> Gateway Tapes —> now I am starting to meditate for the first time in my life. And having an absurd amount of synchronicities and generally feeling.. well, awake. So again my question is, what are the drones/NHI behind the drone activity doing to cause this “awakening”?",
        "Answer": "Blatantly showing humanity they are not alone and activating the 'sleepers' such as yourself to get up and do your part in \"elevating the mass consciousness, collective earth, galactic, and universal spirit.\" That last quote was directly from my contacts. I have ideas of what it means but perhaps you do as well.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_40",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Sorry this is so long. I am just utterly fascinated by this moment, and feeling a strong sense of being on the right path. I have always had claircognizant/telepathic/psychic moments throughout my life but have never tried to purposefully use them. I have used law of attraction “spells” that worked a little too well and really frightened me, like I was using a force that I could not adequately pay back. Suddenly feeling like the moment is here to dive in, but I want to be careful. Thank you for reading this.",
        "Answer": "It's okay. It's clear you are \"one of the awakened.\" Speaking personally, I suppose this is also a lesson for me that I do have to guide others like yourself to some extent (although I have to be careful how) because I understand how lonely, frustrating and infuriating it can be, especially when you are being gaslit, told you're crazy, or that it's a waste of time etc. What I'll tell you is that you need to trust your intuition and do not listen to the lower minds stuck in the \"matrix\" or the beliefs/ideas/ideologies that sustain the mirage of the \"system.\" I'll happily answer other questions, but the more sensitive ones will have to be via DM for your personal information.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_41",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Just for clarification, in point 1 is the end point something more like this person will achieve certain things in their material life or is it more towards the spiritual like this person will be able to communicate telepathically eventually? Or are end points the death of each individual? Could you possibly give an example of an end point",
        "Answer": "1 - There are relative end points. End of a goal (e.g., getting a dream job, becoming more telepathic, law of attraction goal complete etc.) end of a journey, end of a chapter, end of an era, end of a year, death, and then there's the \"ultimate end\" at the \"end of time\" which is a \"re-integration\" into the GCS. Ironically, the GCS doesn't even \"end\" there either. Apparently, it keeps going even after the \"ultimate end\" into a new phase/simulation. Even NHI are still wrapping their heads around this. Also, regarding 'death' - well, I think you get the obvious by now.\n2 - Death is not an \"end\" either, as you will \"reincarnate.\" The only \"individuality\" lost is a \"moment in time.\" Remember my example with the table and Home Depot? Well, a table isn't a table (as an \"individual distinction\") until you assemble it, which requires time to literally do so. Before that, it's just \"parts in a box.\" The same applies to you. The \"individuum\" of \"time\" you can consider to be your \"individuality\" is an \"assembly\" of space and time. Thus, the true \"individual\" is simultaneously everything that created it/was it/will be it (e.g., genes from your parents, atoms, oxygen, 'we're all stars' etc.)\n3- As another poster asked me re. what parts I have not figured out in the puzzle - it's the \"ultimate end goal\" which, as I type this, I realize my \"human-3D brain\" just has difficulty accepting the true nature of reality as an eternity stretched in all directions exponentially, and not a strict linearity. The GCS just somehow continues expanding through past, present and future without any true apparent \"end,\" only relative \"pit stops.\" Good luck understanding this, I'd love to hear your own thoughts too.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_42",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Also you mentioned certain NHI created religion, your referring to only Abrahamic religions correct? And would you know what group of NHI these were or what were their intentions?",
        "Answer": "I do not know all of the groups, but what I can confirm is that all religions were, more or less, created and/or influenced by NHI. The group I am in contact with assisted to a certain degree. That's all I can reveal for now. Religion is supposed to be \"abandoned\" and the cracks in it are there to be painfully obvious for any rational thinking human. It's a primitive device for primitive sentience to realize higher truths eventually.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_43",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "And when you say human beings feed off of each other’s energy also, are these humans doing this consciously (intentionally, & they are aware of what their doing) or sub consciously (unintentionally but doing it cause it makes them feel good)?",
        "Answer": "Both. For 98% of the world, it's unconscious because as a rule of thumb, earth people are extremely underdeveloped.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_44",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Last question, also if NHI made religion and there is no God as mentioned in religious texts, then the concept of Heaven or Hell is invalidated (theres no such thing) correct?",
        "Answer": "No. The closest thing to a \"true God\" = GCS. The closest thing to hell = current earth/sentience making their lives \"hell\" by stupid rules, ordinances, beliefs, war, terror, racism, xenophobia, overpopulation, genocide, nuclear warfare, idiotic social media influencers, celebrities (of all kinds), etc. whereas the closest thing to \"heaven\"= living in truth and creating a society/world based on it.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_45",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Thank you! Is there a need to protect one's energy when experimenting with consciousness expansion? If so, how?",
        "Answer": "Absolutely. This can be trained by using the mind to focus on \"blocks.\" For example, you can use pictorial imagery in the imagination of \"shielding\" yourself. At an adept-enough level, pictorial imagery isn't even needed. Ultimately, what matters is the feeling. Meditation helps with this and of course the self-KNOWING above belief that you CAN.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_46",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "What would you say about the idea that Jesus, Buddha, Krishna were hybridized (human with NHI-mixed DNA, in a greater proportion than normal), and that they were 'planted' to accelerate consciousness evolution?",
        "Answer": "There's some truth to this, but it's not only these figures known throughout religion. It's also less physical DNA hybridization and more of a certain \"soul implantation.\" In other words, through technology (and higher forces but I will not get into that), it's possible to \"influence\" the birth of a specific spirit type. This is precisely how you have \"humans with alien spirits.\" The starseed theory has some truth to it but beware of spiritualist and esoteric communities. There is a lot of disinformation. Some of us have what you'd describe as an \"alien soul\" connected to some of these NHI, which is why they are interested/assist some of us. We're related in a sense.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_47",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Anything more about manifestation, any important points that expand on the idea of \"what the mind is set to brings forth reality\"? Is letting go vital? There's an idea that as one reconnects more with their True Self/Higher Mind, synchronicities and manifestation in one's highest favour become automatic, is that accurate? Would you say that the simulation responds to feeling as well as thought?",
        "Answer": "You've already answered your own questions here. The only thing I'd add is the less doubt and the more confidence/knowing you CAN, the more the \"reality\" or \"actuality\" is brought into physical, tangible form.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_48",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "One of the most prominent ideas in the Consciousness-NHI line of thought, shared by many separate sources, is the idea of a 'rapture' event, where higher-consciousness humans will enter a new dimension separate from lower-consciousness humans, i.e. New Earth/4th density. Is it accurate and what is your understanding of this idea?",
        "Answer": "There's some truth to this but I am not privy to reveal everything at this time, apparently. What I can tell you is that it's not going to happen in the sense of a biblical rapture. This is all I can reveal for now.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_49",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "If the GCS is the central singularity connecting all spaces and times, how does it reconcile or manage the apparent chaos and randomness within individual universes or timelines?",
        "Answer": "There’s a “purification” process or “data refinement” process before it reaches the GCS. There are several layers or “filters” data passes through before it reaches the GCS, which is at such a “high purity” (so to speak) that the data passing through it must “comply” to its “wavelength.” The energetic state of the GCS, from our point of view, is seemingly “holographic” and massless, yet it “inputs” what you can discern as “unalterable” “commands” to all proceeding layers that even “higher beings” beyond physical spacetime cannot “override.”",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_50",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "How do the laws of physics, as we understand them, arise from or align with the underlying nature of the GCS, and are they truly universal across all dimensions and realities?",
        "Answer": "The laws of physics are relative based the position of space and the position of space is based on the flow of its time. Since space can be warped, time can too. Remember how Newton assumed that time is absolute across the cosmos, then Einstein, seemingly, a heretic at the time, presumed the opposite? The same applies here, even for Einstein’s relativity which is not absolute for ALL space and time, only localities. The human race has to move past their absolutist nature, which is deeply encouraged from religion and cults, and affects even science to this day.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_51",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "In your understanding, what is the mechanism by which consciousness interfaces with spacetime? Does it operate as a wave, particle, or something beyond our current scientific models?",
        "Answer": "Particles and waves are actually intermixed on a quantum level, so the answer is both. The brain contains electromagnetic fields, and consciousness exists on this field in the quantum realm in an adjacent dimension. It is a series of quantum-interconnected waves that, on a larger “particle” scale, eventually animates/interacts with electromagnetism and by extension, particles such as photons, amongst others. Very basic, simple example whilst skipping many parts: GCS->(Countless “filter layers”)->Spirit->Consciousness-o-Mind->Physicality.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_52",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "If all beings and objects are fragments of the GCS, how does the process of individuation—becoming a distinct \"self\"—serve the greater purpose of universal reintegration? I tend to believe that experience is what expands consciousness, which contributes to and expands the ultimate \"intelligent infinity\". Curious your take on this.",
        "Answer": "Your thoughts are more or less on the right track. Basically, individuum as a sole unit is an “aspect” or “mini-GCS” of its own. Everything is contributing in some way or another to the collective whole, almost like a hivemind with “singularity” points. Picture it like a developer who, instead of manually using search engines to educate himself on a topic, deploys multiple bots to fetch data. It’s much more efficient, less time consuming, and eventually brings more accurate knowledge to what that person is seeking. Another example would be with a supermassive black hole at the center of a galaxy that both holds and sustains a galaxy, yet, from time to time, stars, gasses, debris etc., fall into the black hole, stimulates it, and the black hole “burps” that matter/data/energy back – leading to either new star formation or galactic regulation.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_53",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "What insights have you gained about the relationship between consciousness and entropy? Could heightened awareness reduce entropy within a given system or reality?",
        "Answer": "Correct. Heightened consciousness, as you describe it, would be a “spirit-mind and awareness that is increasingly ‘closer’ to the GCS.” In this regard, the “closer” one’s consciousness, and by extension, ‘spirit’ is to the GCS, the more it can draw upon the GCS’s “infinite nature” in the lower, “physical” realm. This can create a variety of effects, nearly too endless to list, but the obvious would be increased knowledge and awareness of reality, stability of mind, emotion, body, soul, better health, more “feats of greatness,” and seeming “superpowers” the average layman deems impossible. Many ‘gods’ in myth, who were mostly ETs, know of this and have done it, displaying these seemingly supernatural capabilities for primitive man. There’s nothing supernatural nor paranormal about it, however. Also, there are limits of course because physical existence is at a very “low” stage of total cosmic-universal and multiversal evolution, let alone the GCS itself.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_54",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "How does the simulation aspect of existence interact with the co-creative potential of sentient beings? Are we actively programming the simulation, or merely responding to it?",
        "Answer": "Both. This is the part about “free will” another poster asked which I’d encourage you to read. Simply put, we are a byproduct of the simulation, and thus, bound to it, but we are also “programmed” to expand upon it “within its parameters.” This is both a failsafe against the GCS destroying itself and its “lower forms” (such as physical life) getting out of hand. Picture it like an MMORPG. You can play a class like a warrior or mage, and you can be much better than the average layman if you put effort into it – making what is seemingly “impossible” to the doubter, possible through you. However, you are still that class at the end of the day.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_55",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Long shot here, but if all dimensions and universes are connected through the GCS, is it possible to map these connections in a way that could guide humanity’s spiritual or scientific exploration?",
        "Answer": "Yes. I am not allowed to give details.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_56",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "What do you think is the ultimate purpose of suffering, both on an individual and cosmic scale? How does it fit into the GCS’s \"pay it forward\" model of growth you mentioned?",
        "Answer": "“Suffering” is temporal and is mostly related to the lower physical dimensions. The higher the evolution, the less the suffering on grander scales. Keep in mind this does not apply to emotions and psychic feeling. These are multiplied tremendously, which is why higher beings very rarely interact with lower life. They can be tremendously “hurt” and “horrified” by what lower and more primitive life forms do, but this suffering they experience can be nullified rather easily. This also applies to “higher souls” or more “advanced spirits” or “future-pulled spirits” existing in a lower spacetime dimension. It is extremely troubling to them, which is perhaps why the so-called “starseeds” suffer greatly on earth and are confused why they are even here.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_57",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "If soul energy can ripple across dimensions, are there practical actions (aside from the core principal of embodying love) that individuals can take to ensure their contributions are constructive rather than harmful? Not sure I'm wording this right, but whenever my answer to a situation is \"love\" I feel that it's shrugged off and ignored as being too generalized and fluffy. Trying to think of other ways to engage in these situations.",
        "Answer": "Personally, I tend to agree with you that “love” – at least the word and the general reception of it – has been sullied, greatly. Love itself is not simply affection, nor white-robe cultist delusions. It’s certainly not ‘being crazy’ either or overstimulated. It’s a “primordial existence-enabling force.” Pay attention to this. Love ‘creates’ existence. It applies not just for physical beings but for seemingly “inanimate” objects like rocks, gasses, dust and so on. According to NHI, these somehow exist because of love. Some other examples are such as one can “love” their career and give all their “power” (love) to it – and thus, achieve great results. This even applies to “love” of evil (e.g., “love” to create weapons) – which will manifest itself to the one putting out that “love.” Of course, evil eventually destroys itself which is apparently some sort of “cosmic” or GCS law as one nears “the end of time.” NHI are very insistent that I impart this message of “love.” There’s a lot more to it. They said you should refer to Amelia Brand’s quote on love from Christopher Nolan’s Interstellar. “Love is the one thing we're capable of perceiving that transcends dimensions of time and space. Maybe we should trust that, even if we can't understand it.”",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_58",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "How do NHIs or higher beings perceive the flow of time differently from us, and what lessons can we learn from their perspective about navigating our own temporal experiences? Ra and other channels/sources I've read mention various \"densities\" of existence that answer this, but i'm curious what your thoughts are on it.",
        "Answer": "Their perception of time is similar to mine in the sense that it transverses in multiple directions and the effects of one point in time, affects another. This was, at first, difficult for my “human-3D” brain to accept, but the more you understand that every “event” which includes actions – ripples outward throughout space – and thus – time, then the more you can be attuned to it. Our clocks we are used to is only a measurement of locality, but locality, as the word implies, does not apply to the gross interstellar. A simple example would be with timezones. If a person in Australia is communicating with you in America, then the present for you is a 12–20-hour difference. Your present versus theirs is different, yet the same. Why? Because you’re in different locations. This is how it works on a cosmic scale with distance creating more and more relativistic effects. Yet, your PRESENT can connect with the person’s PRESENT in Australia and somehow, you are in different times. Think about this very carefully, especially concerning computing and internet technologies along with the upcoming quantum computing being gradually available to the public. Now, think about it if you had to ‘send a letter’ across the seas to your friend in Australia versus messaging them online. Starting to get it?",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_59",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "What is the nature of memory in the GCS? Is it analogous to a universal \"record\" or \"database,\" and can individuals access this directly?",
        "Answer": "Yes and no. It cannot be accessed directly consciously, but subconsciously, which can then be “translated” into conscious perception. As a rule of thumb, the higher the consciousness/spirit/closeness to the GCS, the greater one’s aptitude to “access” this data. It’s much more than just past or future lives. An untrained consciousness can go insane from it, especially if they are living in a world that gaslights them for thinking outside the primitive, artificial “norm.”",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_60",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "If analog computing can tap into quantum electromagnetic fields, could it truly become a tool for bridging our understanding of the physical and spiritual realms?",
        "Answer": "It’s not just analog computing. Electromagnetic fields are present everywhere. There are greater concentrations of it, such as a computer, the human brain, amongst technology and natural phenomena etc. Anything that has an electromagnetic field has a quantum link. If it can be accessed via quantum, it can be transmitted elsewhere. As a rule of thumb, the higher the speed/rate of information transfer, the higher/more developed the person. Think about this carefully. See how when the internet became publicly available how mankind’s knowledge and collective consciousness skyrocketed in just a few decades? Same idea applies here, but on a universal (and greater) scale.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_61",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "How might humanity’s collective awareness or spiritual development influence the GCS’s evolution, and vice versa? Are we shaping each other in real-time?",
        "Answer": "Yes, as are countless other worlds, spaces, times, and dimensions. So, if there is a “pollution” that is “preventing the flow” at the top, then “forces up top,” come to deal with it so the “dam can break.” On earth, there’s what you can describe as a “spiritual stifling” which is affecting the mass consciousness. Since everything is interconnected, what happens here is affecting “elsewhere” and these “elsewhere” places and their “inhabitants” aren’t particularly happy about it. However, this works in the positive too. Since everything and everyone at all times and spaces are drawing and sharing data across the GCS “network” we are also receiving natural evolutive-data to push mankind forward. Progress is inevitable. It cannot be stopped. It is nature’s way. Whoever or whatever tries to block it for whatever reason must “answer” for it, sooner or later.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_62",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Are there beings or phenomena that exist entirely outside of the GCS’s influence, or does its connectivity truly encompass all things?",
        "Answer": "It’s connectivity encompasses all things. Nothing can exist outside it because it is everything, everywhere, all at once and nothing, nowhere.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_63",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Finally, have your contacts/sources ever specifically mentioned \"The Council of Saturn\" when discussing the guardians of our particular system? Have they mentioned, or do you have any insight into, any particular order of guardianship over our planet? I try (mostly unsuccessfully) to keep track of the various ones I come across in my readings that I feel are somewhat genuine, but it’s very difficult to discern truth in this area as I'm sure you are aware.",
        "Answer": "They have not mentioned those, nor do I have knowledge of it, but what I can tell you is that my contacts are keeping this world from blowing up.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_64",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Out of curiosity, do you consult or ask for guidance from your sources as you answer questions or is everything within here pulled from existing knowledge/wisdom you’ve already received?",
        "Answer": "It's pulled from my existing knowledge and wisdom that I've received. Sometimes they might \"barge\" in with particular \"quotes\" or specifics I should say, which I usually make known, but for the most part, they trust me to impart the knowledge. You have to keep in mind I've been prepared for this role for nearly three decades. My contacts reach me via secluded telepathy and the occasional up-close encounter. It's full-on conversations/dialogue. Since I \"blend\" into the public, the average person wouldn't recognize me beside \"feeling\" an energy that, to them, can invoke feelings of higher \"love/truth/energy expansion\" - but sometimes, this can create insecurities in the person if I do not shield the magnetic reach of my telepathy. I've been called a god, an angel, and other titles, which is precisely why I am hiding my identity because I want to \"blend in\" without any worship or praise. I do not want any cult following nor do I wish to be known outside the pseudonym I will use to disclose relevant information. My message is important, not me. As far as the telepathy goes, you must understand it works like this: What one has within the consciousness is what the outer telepathic connection (including regular people, btw) connecting to you can utilize to \"send information.\" If the consciousness is limited; lacking the necessary data etc., then the telepathic exchange can be confused, misinterpreted, and outright false. That's why these roles take decades to adequately step into and they require a lifetime of dedication to said missions. It's extremely frustrating to say at the least, especially when you do not want to put your loved ones at risk. There is much that you have to keep from them for their own safety. Do not trust \"contactees\" who are eager to spread their name, face, and image. These are usually dead giveaways of fakers, liars, hoaxers, frauds, grifters, and thieves. True telepathic contactees will most likely want to remain anonymous.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_65",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Who are the Greys and why are they engaging with humanity? Who are the Mantids and why are they engaging with humanity? Who are the Reptilians and why are they engaging with humanity? Who are the Nordic beings and why are they engaging with humanity? Why are experiencers interacting with beings of such appearances the most?",
        "Answer": "I had to directly consult my contacts before answering this question because it is extremely dangerous to post this information publicly at this time. What I am allowed to say is this: most of these ideas of ETs such as “Nordic” aliens, including Pleiadians, and also, “Plejaren,” along with many other “visual concepts of aliens” are not their actual likeliness, name, nor their appearance. These are either straight up frauds or “imaginative reaches” from contactees in most cases with very, very, very few exceptions of truth. Sometimes, a person can connect or pull “data” from the soul-matrix-mass-consciousness, which is also called “Akashic records” among other mystical and esoteric names. Any ET/NHI arriving or on earth can have bits of their “data” – including “ideas” of their appearances, motives etc., pulled from this interconnected soul-consciousness-matrix and unconsciously grasped, then “translated” in the connecting person’s consciousness using the information/awareness/data/knowledge in that person’s awareness. This is how some writers can naturally come up with ideas for aliens (e.g., Star Trek, Mass Effect and so on). If the person’s mind is favored or biased in a certain direction, or in the case with religious people, can only think that ETs are strictly angels or demons – then they will project this idea onto the ETs/NHI and see them as such (e.g., Mothman “prophecies”). In several cases, ETs allow this because if the public were to know of their real appearances, it can create telepathic links that can negatively affect them. This is also why phones cannot take clear photos/videos of UFOs/UAP etc., as is the case with aliens even if they were in front of you because they are purposely using electromagnetic distortion via apparatuses. Admiral Byrd’s encounter with “Nazi aliens” is an example of his own projection. Since, at the time, there was much paranoia, fear, hatred and mistrust of Nazis and Germany in general, he projected this image when he encountered the beings there because of fear of the unknown. That is all I can disclose about his encounter. Now, regarding the so-called “Nordics” which is not a term I’d ever use – there are “human-looking” ETs and some of them have European-Scandinavian-like features, but there are also members of this group who are “colored,” which would be a shocker for the racists and white supremacists who are projecting their own biases onto real ET/NHI. This may sound harsh, and it is no offense to any of the good people there, but you need to be very careful with any German-related information regarding ETs, especially from Switzerland. The latter country in particular is filled with much evil and is host to thousands of cults that are contributing toward very negative and dark influence that real ETs, particularly the good ones, are VERY, VERY upset about. I will not mention the name of any particular group, but as a rule of thumb, you shouldn’t trust any information coming from Switzerland regarding ETs. Concerning greys and the “mantids” as you call them, they exist. Some are capable of shapeshifting; others can use technology to influence your mind to see them as human-looking or something else altogether. I am not allowed to speak of what you describe as “reptilians.”",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_66",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Which group is working directly with clandestine hidden human power groups?",
        "Answer": "I am not allowed to reveal this publicly at this time. All I can say is there are at least two of them.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_67",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Which groups are in conflict with each other?",
        "Answer": "This is more complex than what most people would assume, and I am not allowed to reveal much of this publicly. What I’ll say is this: defectors on multiple sides exist. For example, I mentioned Germany above, but do you believe that every person in Nazi Germany during WW2 was evil? There were some German patriots who couldn’t stand what Hitler, and the Nazi regime were doing and wanted to stand up to it, such as the case with operation Valkyrie. This is also happening with some NHI/ET groups on earth, though most groups keep to themselves. Not each and every single one of them because they belonged to a particular faction are outright evil nor pledge their allegiance to their original group, federation, or world. “Higher beings” who are beyond physical spacetime have no allegiance to any group except for “keeping things in order” for the GCS at “the end of time.” NHI/ET dabbling here on earth has “messed up” things in other parts of the interconnected “grand cosmos” and some of these “higher beings” and forces are not pleased with the consequences of ET/NHI actions on earth.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_68",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Why are many experiencers also able to engage with beings that appear to represent themselves as deities, goddesses and other such mythological entities. Where do these beings fit in with the more traditional \"ET\" like NHI?",
        "Answer": "The reply above should be sufficient re. the groups you asked of. What I’ll add is this: sometimes ET/NHI can only connect with what is “acceptable” to the person’s mind. Some groups will not force themselves and their true nature onto the person. They’ll allow them to perceive within the relativity of what is acceptable to the person’s consciousness. This is largely in part due to the matrix “bubble” we grow up in here on earth that makes it extremely difficult for the average person to accept truths outside what they’ve been taught. Contactees are no exception to this rule, as most of them are still fearful and uncertain. Understandably so. Contactees walk the uncomfortable line between “two worlds” and many of them can be driven to alienation, madness, depression, and other mental illnesses as a result, especially when society stigmatizes them. This makes it even more difficult for contactees to properly understand who/what is contacting them and their true nature. This is why I stress the importance of adequate mental stability, emotional health, physical well-being and spiritual soundness, which is why I strongly recommend meditation, especially for contactees, who, more than the average person, need to be very, very, very careful with the “energy” they are sending and receiving via all inputs/outputs.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_69",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Explain everything about the abduction phenomenon. To extreme detail.",
        "Answer": "Not happening, not to “extreme detail” because that is extremely dangerous for me and you. I am not willing to put myself at risk to do so, nor anyone else. What I can say is that abductions are akin to the example of us, humans, tagging wildlife and keeping track of them, their health, biology, genetics, and development. Not all groups engage in abduction.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_70",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Explain the implants and list out all they can do and what they are all for.",
        "Answer": "I can’t and won’t because the information is too dangerous on a public forum. The answer is similar to my reply above. Let’s just say these are the “trackers.”",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_71",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Explain the 3, 33's and the 333's.",
        "Answer": "3-3-3 is how it should be written, which goes into 3-6-9-12-15-18-21 and so on. This is the spiral pattern of eternity. It’s the direct spiral string of the GCS. Fibonacci sequence got some numbers correct, but not all.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_72",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Explain the triangles.",
        "Answer": "You’ll need to be more specific. Are you referring to the triangle UFOs? Pyramids? Geometry? Something else?",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_73",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Which specific group of NHI are you in contact with and what exactly do they look like?",
        "Answer": "Groups operate by region. There are different groups and their allies operating in Europe, North America, South America, Russia, China, Japan, Australia & New Zealand, along with other continents, including Antarctica and the Arctic. They are not always “flying around” to say “hi” and have conversation. Most are leaving phased or cloaked devices (e.g., the ‘orbs’) to “pick up” on relevant data, not just about “contactees,” who can be prone to a special-syndrome complex; thinking everything is about them, but on other important data such as biometrics, regional stability, weather, general health of a population, soul-energy, and more. Most ET/NHI are not concerned with contacting people as much as believers and contactees assume. There are far more important tasks. The good ones are concerned with WMDs, nuclear warfare, international tension, the weapons industry, radiation leaks, and other hazards and conflicts to mankind, including cult and religious power over the soul. I have to be very careful with how I say what comes next because it can reveal my location, which I am not willing to do. I’ll say this: some NHI/ET operate in compartmentalized groups who share intel with each other. I’ve recently been transferred from one contact group to another because of “changing” my location. These groups are working together. The main ones I work with which I can reveal to you are a mixture of “tall greys/mantids” (if you wish to call them that) and the human-looking ETs that I wouldn’t recommend calling “Nordics.” Some are working together, amongst other races that I have not personally contacted. What you also need to understand is this: contactees can be in extreme danger with the information they are giving out, especially if your identity can be traced. As I said above, I am not willing to put either of us (and others) at risk for internet curiosity because it’s also not my mission as a ground agent. My task is to elevate the consciousness of mankind in preparation for upcoming events, which I can do without even citing my connection to my “friends from above.”",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_74",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "Some of what you speak of regarding this GCS reminds me of something I was shown regarding the torus. Am I connecting this right or off base?",
        "Answer": "Yes. See: https://www.inwardboundnetwork.com/torus-meditation among others. The “grand cosmos” which includes the GCS at the “heart” or “center” has an identical shape, though it is far “stringier” and more sophisticated. I may draw some examples.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_75",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "I don't understand what you mean when you say NHI talk about us all being one connected to one ultimate God/GCS when you also state that NHI encourage a pantheistic view of god?",
        "Answer": "/ˌpæn.θiˈɪs.tɪk/ (also pantheist) showing or holding a belief in many or all gods, or the belief that God exists in, and is the same as, all things, animals, and people within the universe: the pantheistic religions of the world. The pantheistic approach to nature is that God is in everything.” Personally, I don’t really like to use the word ‘God’ as it gives the idea of a “person,” which is inherently wrong. Basically, all of us are “it” in the beginning of time as The Source energy itself, here in the now as a fragment, and then in the future as The Source once more. We are The Creator and co-creators at the same time. Baruch Spinoza has some rudimentary, yet solid ideas of this truth. The GCS is the “heart” or “singularity”-point of the ALL or ‘God.’ For reference, picture that your hands, arms, legs, feet, belly, etc., are all “part” of you and your brain is the central core that everything connects to. The GCS would be the ‘core’, but the other parts of the body are part/working with the GCS, so we can consider “one human” is the “sum of all their components.” This is the case for not just life, but literally EVERYTHING. Rocks, atoms, gasses, dust, water, “void-space”, quarks; EVERYTHING is ‘God’ (or a piece of ‘God’) or the ALL with the central singularity point being the most potent of them all.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_76",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "You have spoken about how people developing their consciousness and psi become more appealing to beings seemingly looking to absorb or utilize their emotional and sexual energy. I have seen this in my work and know some experiencers who have frozen in their development due to odd NHI activity in their home when in heightened emotional states and or sexual states which feels extremely intrusive and alarming for those in question. Even for people used to dealing with more intense levels of contact find this aspect of the phenomenon to be a roadblock. This does not happen for everyone but for those who do it blocks their development. I also know those who are highly gifted but pause on their development due to a desire to not have increased activity in their house as they have children and are highly protective. How did you overcome these factors to keep up with your own development? What advice would you give to experiencers who have paused in their journey due to these factors?",
        "Answer": "Well, this has to be a personal decision that we cannot and must not force – that is to say – if these individuals wish to continue their development and task. The truth is there is a “soul-feeding” going on, so to speak, and both human and ET/NHI can do this; sometimes accidentally (they are NOT perfect, they make a lot of mistakes), and in some cases, malevolent entities that are “leeching.” What I’d recommend is that the person has to decide for themselves if they wish to continue and come to terms with the fact that all contactees are in a soul-energetic trade whether they like it or not. Can this be invasive? Perhaps, but my personal belief is that this is a fear sprouted from our upbringings that do not teach us the true nature of reality. Simply put, everything is in a give/take exchange. It’s just the way it works. Contactees “pull” on ET/NHI as well, and this can be very draining to them, simply because of the difference of evolutionary levels. If you look at it from that perspective, is it fair that we are taking and never giving? Many of these ET/NHI are beings too. They are not invulnerable, nor unlimited. Think about this carefully.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_77",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "All distractions from what? Meditating 24/7 and nothing else?",
        "Answer": "It depends on the contactee’s level of spirit-consciousness development and their willingness to perform their task/role. The more of the demand of the task as a ground agent, the likelihood the necessity of developing and attuning skills, which includes A LOT of meditation, to say at the least. There’s no way around it, nor any shortcuts. I have been meditating for decades, with the past 15 years being anywhere between 10 to 15 hours per day of specific types of meditations to enhance my abilities for my tasks. To develop higher psi skills, better education, understand the true nature of reality and so on; it cannot come from being distracted/being consumed in the mirage of a “society” you live in. The more you consume yourself in the “ground level” society our families, friends, etc. live in (who aren’t connected to contactee tasks), and their intrigues (e.g., social media influence), the more your potency drops. This is how it works. That is why it is so difficult and why many people cannot begin to comprehend how truly life-consuming and lonesome being a ‘contactee’ really is. A lot of people are in this just to be entertained or to promote their image. That is why there are levels of contactees and most are contacted unconsciously because they are unwilling to give up their ‘ground-level’ lives and the belief systems connected therein. Understandably so, since it is extremely frustrating and difficult to be a contactee in a world that lives in lies and delusion when you’re being that bridge for truth and bringing forth a higher reality. The higher the potency of the contactee, the more the isolation, even when you “blend into” society and are surrounded by loving family and friends.",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_78",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "While I think I get more of what you are trying to say here I don't vibe with a lot of your example. We are a social species and we learn and develop and grow from our interactions with one another. Creativity and coming together as part of a social group \"Parties/video games\" etc can and do have spiritually elevating qualities to them. Of course intent and set and setting applies. My own NHI have been extremely responsive to me gather groups of experiencers into social settings to talk share grow and bond. But have also encouraged me to not forget about family get togethers and see an importance there too. I have done support calls with experiencers while both of us were playing minecraft together. Which was heavily appreciated by both the experiencers personal NHI contact and my own beings. Indeed my ability to heal others via social settings and creating social environments where people gather as groups and talk from the heart while also have fun seems to be something that is considered highly valuable by a number of NHI beings I've come across as well as my own.",
        "Answer": "As pointed out yesterday, there was a misunderstanding. Hopefully, my response above would already begin to clarify. However, I’d like to address specific topics you mentioned here more directly. First, creativity and art, such as music, literature, video games, movies/cinema, among others, are VERY, VERY, VERY good. Christopher Nolan’s works are exceptionally elevating to the consciousness, among others like the game Spore, and in some cases, Second Life, though it can be used wrongly and indulged in escapism. The intent matters greatly. All things in moderation. You should be aware that I was a professional gamer and was sponsored to compete at a high tier level. The amount of hand-eye-coordination to neuroplasticity is nothing short of electrifying and stimulating to the consciousness. The same applies to good, harmonic music, and not music blasting lyrics about drugs, violence, over-sexuality, darkness, death, and the discordant “harmonics” associated therein. Same applies to movies, TV shows and the like, along with pornography designed to create shock and awe such as Game of Thrones. All this stimulates the soul field in many ways than you may assume, which I can get into, if you wish. Now, regarding your specific connections with family and friends – I believe this is your task and I encourage you to continue it. All contactees aren’t here for the same missions. I am at a level that I can no longer be among crowds very much any longer, even friends and family whom I love dearly. Their wavelengths are too “in the system” and it creates more damage to me – as naturally – whether you like it or not, we are ALL exchanging soul-energy; hence the feedback-loop. The higher the developed the lifeform/consciousness, the more you will be drained because like a parent, you are giving more to the child than visa versa. I’ve also been in various teams, and even led a community of advanced individuals, so I am well aware of the “healing effect” you mentioned and the exchange of energy. However, for me, I went “too far” ahead (which was necessary for my task) and the “exchange” became too tilted that I was drained even without my loved ones, friends, etc., wishing to do so. Your NHI contacts encourage you to do so because that is part of your mission which I am also encouraging you to continue doing. The world needs contactees like yourself just as much as it needs the extremely rare ones like me, who have a very specific purpose with serious, life-altering demands. I cannot work a “regular job” and I am sponsored by certain parties who are well aware of my abilities. What I’ll also say is this: that ‘thing’ I asked for had to do with a loved one. That loved one is the only one capable of giving me the feedback-loop I need that allows me to continue my task while blending into society as a supposed “normie.”",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    },
    {
        "Title": "QA1_79",
        "Category": "Uncategorized",
        "Tags": [],
        "Question": "I'd also like to ask, regarding your many years developing your psi/telepathic abilities - do you have a course or guide or book or material you could recommend for Experiencers to develop theirs? Many experiencers I know struggle with this and just wing it.",
        "Answer": "My contacts are insistent that I do not recommend any work other than what will be released by “JR” sometime in the near future. Too much of what is out there is polluted, despite some half-truths, and I understand how frustrating it can be to constantly be “reading between the lines” due to the sheer amount of misinformation, distortion, and sometimes, honest mistakes out there. Just wait for this to come, as it is designed for those like yourself, among other “starseeds.” (I hesitate using that term because the spiritualist, esoteric and mystic communities are perhaps even more polluted than the UFO/UAP/NHI)",
        "MessageType": "Q & A - JR",
        "OriginalPostTitle": "(Q & A) Part 1",
        "OriginalPostURL": "https://www.jrprudence.com/post/q-a-part-1"
    }
]